Oh, my God.
Oh, thank you, Kodaka. That was really nice of you.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
You know what? Hold on a sec.
Let me get one.
I appreciate that, Kodaka.
You're very welcome, Aoi.
I guess you can go ahead and follow me this way if you want to.
Carrying two boxes this heavy at once
makes it seem like you want them to fall.
I don't.
I'm just trying to make up time on my student council work
since I skipped it for a week.
You skipped for a week?
Hey, do you mind telling me
why you were so set on destroying the Neighbors Club?
Because Senna is exceptionally gifted,
and she should be somewhere appropriate for her gifts.
What do you mean, somewhere appropriate?
Face it. Senna Kashiwazaki is unbelievably talented
and needed a better way to make use of those talents.
Your club was just a waste of her time.
Wow.
So then, you tried to disband the Neighbors Club
for the sake of your so-called mortal enemy?
Yes.
If you say so.
I guess she has a point.
Senna would be an asset to any club she decided to join.
It's not just her, either.
Yozara and Rika have that super smart thing going on for them.
And then you have Yukimura and Kobito,
who are both popular.
Maybe Aoi's right.
Maybe there's really no point to even having the Neighbors Club.
Oh, I'm just kidding.
You what?
I don't like Senna.
She gets everything her little heart desires,
so I just wanted her to realize
she might lose something one day.
So, in other words, I'm wicked jealous of her.
Well, the funny thing is, you're wrong.
She doesn't have everything.
Yeah?
What doesn't she have?
She doesn't have friends.
Jeez, are you okay?
Why are you laughing?
I forgot you have such a great sense of humor.
You're hilarious, you know that?
I'm not falling for it, though.
There's not a single person in the whole world
who doesn't have friends.
I wouldn't be so sure.
It was really sweet of you
to try and cheer me up after what I did.
Thank you again, Kodaka.
Huh?
Almost there.
You were a big help.
I couldn't have done it without you.
You still have more, yeah?
I can help you with those.
No, I can't ask you to do that.
This stuff got piled up
because of the neighbor's club.
So I'm partly to blame.
I can't not help you.
Don't you need to go meet with that club, though?
Well, we're not really big
on planning activities every day.
So if we have other stuff to do first,
it's not a big deal.
Why do I feel like I have to make excuses?
Weird.
Well, on the bright side, we made it halfway.
I guess so.
Well, you two seem to be working well together.
Hinata, what did you come out here for?
I heard some extremely nice individuals
started helping you with your chores.
I thought I'd come check on you and thank him myself.
Oh, uh, hello.
I'm Kodaka Hasegawa from Class 2-5.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's totally you.
Wait, you know who he is?
Nope, no clue.
Then what the heck was that reaction about?
I don't know.
Call it a whim.
I'm Hinata, the student council president.
It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, cool.
Hey, I was wondering, why are you helping Aoi?
This is a lot of work.
You guys must be, like, dating or something, yeah?
No, we're not dating.
Besides, Kodaka probably already has a girlfriend.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Um, no.
Come on, you're telling me
that you're not dating anyone from the neighbor's club?
No, I am not.
It just isn't like that with them, okay?
Hmm, probably for the best.
What do you mean?
What's for the best?
Well, if you think about it,
you're the only boy in the whole club,
so you're surrounded by girls.
If you dated one of them,
the whole atmosphere would get,
like, way awkward.
Yeah, that's for sure.
So, if you're not her boyfriend,
why are you helping out?
Because he happens to be one of those guys
who comes to the rescue
when he sees someone in trouble.
Oh, my.
Well, isn't that fancy?
Keep up the good work, kid.
Okay, I think that's it.
For the last time,
thanks so much for your help.
Don't worry about it.
It's not a problem.
See you later.
Oh, hey, uh, Kodaka.
Yeah?
You seem like you're a cool guy.
Want to join the student council with us?
Huh?
We just lost our general affairs person,
so we're looking for a replacement,
if you're interested.
You should definitely join.
It'll be a ton of fun, I promise.
Really?
I'm surprised you'd want to work with me.
Actually, the council only has girls on it right now.
I think it would be nice for us to have a guy around.
Honestly, Kodaka,
you would be perfect on the student council.
I don't know.
Haven't you heard the way people talk about me?
I don't want to bring you guys down.
I don't get it.
What's wrong with this super cool
bad boy chic real life haver?
Yeah, thank you,
but you're the only one who thinks that about me.
You're welcome.
See, most people don't think I'm bad boy chic.
They assume I'm just bad.
I get called a delinquent and all sorts of mean things.
It's because I have weird hair and a grumpy face.
That's true.
Your hair does get attention,
and you have evil-looking eyes.
There, you see?
Putting me on the student council
would wreck your reputation,
and I don't want to do that.
Only fools judge on appearances,
and I simply don't care what fools think.
Are you going to let idiots decide
what you can and can't do?
What's the matter, Kodika?
You look a little dazed.
No, I mean, yes, I'm fine.
Good to hear.
So, are you going to join?
No, no, I'm sorry.
I think the student council
might be a little too much for me.
But if all you need is more manual labor,
just let me know.
I'd be happy to help out
whenever and wherever I can.
Plus, I'm almost always free.
Really?
The library asked for us
to help with a project,
so if you'd like to come by tomorrow,
that would be so great.
Sure.
Count on me to be there.
Mm-hmm.
That's a perfect answer.
A week went by so fast,
I barely even realized
what was happening.
I ended up helping the student council
pretty much every day.
It's kind of funny.
All the kids at school
think Hinata is like a god
for getting that punk in line.
Just a second.
Don't forget to sweat every day.
She's getting even more popular than before.
My reputation's the same, though.
Holy crap, I'm sorry!
No surprise there.
I haven't set foot
into our club room since then.
Don't get me wrong,
the neighbor's club
still means a lot to me.
But after running out on them like that,
I couldn't go back.
I don't know why.
I just couldn't.
Look who I finally found.
Oh.
Yuki Mura.
Big brother.
Oh.
Hey, Yuki Mura.
What's up?
I heard a despicable gang captured you
and that they were forcing you
to do manual labor.
So I have come to your rescue.
You know, that's really rude to say.
Kodaka's helping us because he's nice
and that's all there is to it.
Seriously?
Is that the truth, brother?
Yeah.
In that case,
I shall help out as well.
No thanks.
And besides,
why would you?
Aren't you the one
who wanted to poison me?
I am.
Why are you wearing
a boy's uniform anyway?
I'm wearing this uniform
because I'm endeavoring
to become a true man.
You want to be a true man?
What does that even mean?
It means I want to be a great man.
What?
You do realize
you're a girl, don't you?
That is of no importance.
True and genuine men
can transcend their birth gender.
Huh?
Have you just been let out
of an insane asylum?
Because you sound kind of crazy.
Big brother,
may I slay that villain, please?
You may not slay
student council members.
I'm sorry, Aoi,
but will you excuse us
for a minute?
Sure.
If that's what you really want.
So tell me,
anything new
at the neighbor's club?
No.
Senna is still totally engrossed
with those video games
about making friends
with girls and stuff.
Man, she just won't give up
on those, will she?
How is everyone else doing?
I'm not sure.
Yozra and Rika
haven't been to the clubroom
for a few days now.
Maria comes by
to have a snack now and again,
but after that, she leaves.
So you and Senna
are the only ones
who are showing up anymore?
Yes.
We're it, I'm afraid.
Oh, great.
What am I supposed
to do about this?
Big brother,
I can carry half of these.
No, they're not heavy.
I'm fine.
Then,
is there any other way
I can be of service to you?
Nah, not today.
Thank you, though.
Yes, I understand.
I shall come back tomorrow.
Hey, Yukimura?
Hmm?
I don't understand
why you're always looking
for some reason to serve me.
You are my sworn brother.
I enjoy helping you
when I can.
Then let me ask you this.
Yes?
Why on earth would anyone
still want to be
my sworn brother?
I mean, come on,
you've got to realize
the truth by now.
I'm not this genuine man
that you want to be.
I'm just pathetic.
I'm just a big, fat, stupid wimp.
I know.
What the?
You agree?
As I said before,
I am your sworn brother.
Ah, okay.
Then explain why
you haven't disowned me already.
Seriously,
what is the point to all this?
Does there really have
to be a point, big brother?
I serve you
because I want to be
by your side.
What other reason
do I need, right?
Ugh.
What would you do
if, um,
if the club was, um,
disbanded?
I would be sad, of course,
but I would be here.
I will continue
to serve you
no matter what.
You're a really cool person,
you know that?
The fact is,
you're too good to me.
Hopefully one day
I'll be worthy enough
to be your big brother.
Kodaka.
Oh, big brother.
Never in my life
have I been so frustrated.
I'm not a boy.
It's one of the worst
feelings ever.
Huh?
You're making my heart
flutter out of control
right now.
If I were a big
and vigorous man,
I would throw caution
to the wind
and take this opportunity
to overpower you
and plunge my raging passion
into your soft
and ready yaoi hole.
Yeah, you lost me
on that one.
Sorry.
It's an awful shame,
don't you agree?
No, but what you're saying
to me is a shame.
Ugh!
Besides,
there's no such thing
as a yaoi hole.
No, that isn't true.
Rinka told me
all about it.
You don't have
a yaoi hole.
Really?
Right, of course she did.
You get me.
It's Rinka.
Please come to the roof
right away.
If you're not here
in three minutes,
Rinka will broadcast
to the whole school
the secret recording
she made of your lovely
and dramatic
boy love reading.
What recording?
Big Brother?
Sorry, I have to go,
but will you take those papers
to the student council room
for me, please?
Of course, I can do that.
Thanks, I owe you one.
Big Brother, wait.
Huh?
Good luck in battle.
Thanks.
Three minutes,
26 seconds.
Huh?
Rinka will let it slide
this time.
Oh, whatever, Rinka.
I bet you don't even
have a recording of me.
Desperate for my boy hole.
My ass is hungry, teacher,
and wants a bite of your...
You seriously recorded that?
Don't act so surprised
with Rinka.
Fine.
What do you want from me?
Rinka doesn't necessarily
want something.
It's more like she wants
to inflict a little torture
upon you,
what with the lying.
After all,
you acted like you valued
the neighbor's club,
but still ran out on us
like a loser.
Look, I'm sorry.
Meek isn't normally
your style.
If it makes you feel
any better,
I know I deserve
anything you say.
So punch me,
kick me,
whatever makes you
feel better.
Whatever you say,
Kodaka.
What are those?
They're a form of artillery.
Rinka can control them
via brainwaves.
The Nine Lives Breaker.
Rinka took the name
from a powerful spell
in Fullmetal Necromancer.
What do they do?
It's probably easier
just to show you.
Shatter the very soul
of Rinka's enemy!
Damn, Rinka.
Don't you think
that's a bit much?
Not really.
Rinka's not strong enough
to cause you pain herself.
But that is hardly
enough reason to allow
you to escape the punishment
that you so richly deserve.
Rinka is rather angry.
So she is going to use
these to train you.
Next time,
you'll think twice
before running away!
I did not run away.
I was just really busy.
A sudden love confession
would throw anyone off.
Rinka's pissed about
your behavior afterwards.
It's been over a week
and you have yet
to come back to the club.
And now what?
You're like new best friends
with that horrible girl
who tried to disband us?
What are you talking about?
I'll always not
my best friend.
So you admit
you're friends with her?
On top of that,
you've started flirting
with the student council president.
Seduced by a sexy older woman.
You're just a sick and twisted
gigolo.
You're wrong, Rinka.
I wasn't seduced
by her sexiness like at all.
But Hinata is cool.
And I do like her personality.
She's not crazy as hell.
Rinka will never forgive you
for that!
Yeah, okay.
That was out of line.
I apologize.
Your personality is great too.
Too late for sorry.
Tell Rinka the truth.
You probably already conveniently
have somehow accidentally
walked in on her naked.
You have, haven't you?
What?
How'd you know about that?
Oh no.
You mean Rinka was actually right?
How could you be
so disgustingly stereotypical?
I can't take much more.
Artillery she controls
with her brainwaves?
Then those carriers
must be the antenna.
Fold attack!
Damn it.
I can't get close enough.
Rinka asked Senna
when she fell for you.
You saved her
from some boys at a pool.
Hold on to that one
so you'll know
you were a man
once upon a time.
It wasn't long
before you tried
to get all up in her gutter.
Shut up!
And you've just been
clearing flags
ever since that day.
I know you stayed
the night at her house.
No, it wasn't like that.
What the hell?
She ended up being your friend
since you were a kid
and your fiancé?
That's a total troll character.
Then take that up with her.
Not that you care,
but because of that
Yozara is completely depressed.
Yeah, I already know.
Yozara and I
have an important past
and she's been using it
for emotional support.
I'd help her
if I knew how.
Important past.
If who you met first
is really that important,
then you might as well
suck on your mom's teats forever.
Emotions aren't just
some experiment
you could control, Rika.
You really don't get it, do you?
But go on.
Keep up the good work
clearing those flags
with one girl after another.
Be that lame anime harem hero
who gets all the girls
because he's just so damn nice.
Yeah, anime harem hero,
I wish.
You know what?
I wish I could give everyone
a happy ending,
but life isn't some romantic anime
and I can't fix what's wrong in life
stumbling around being oblivious
and nice all the time.
Believe it or not,
this isn't very easy for me either.
I know that I'm not the hero.
I will most likely
never be the hero.
Surprise,
I'm just as scared as you are.
So you take it out on Rika?
Real classy.
I never said I was classy.
I never said I was anything.
The club is a place I've never had.
It's like a miracle.
A home where freaks like us
can just be who we are
without feeling like
we had to hold back.
I don't want to screw that up,
but that is exactly
what I was doing
and you know it.
This whole thing is meaningless
if it ends up
making you hold back.
You've pretended to be
the oblivious guy
since day one
and when you couldn't
fake it anymore,
you ran away.
What's the point
of loving somewhere
so much that you feel
like you have to leave
just so you can protect it?
We never asked you
to sacrifice yourself
at the altar
of the neighbor's club
so don't be stupid!
You think you can talk?
Fuck you!
Who's playing
the sacrifice card again?
Oh, you pretend
to be Little Miss Class Cloud.
Meanwhile,
you never stop working
behind the scenes
to make sure everything
is perfect.
You're too damn good
to all of us!
And here you are
taking the thankless role again.
You're just as guilty
of holding back as I am.
Both of us
are doing our best.
What the hell else
do you want?
Come on.
What do you think
Rika wants?
What did we start
this dumb club for?
For friends!
I want friends!
All I want are friends!
Friends!
Rika, sorry, Kotika.
She lied about controlling
those things
with her brainwaves.
Then what are
the ears for?
They're just a toy
that uses brainwaves
to make them twitch.
Really?
That's kind of cool.
You sure are a tough fighter,
Rika.
Same to you.
The truth is,
Rika can't stand anymore.
She's exhausted.
Yeah, me too.
Hey, Kotika.
What's up?
If you can't fix things
on your own,
please,
ask Rika for help.
Remember,
Rika is literally a genius.
She eats impossible problems
for breakfast.
So, hey, Rika?
Yeah?
What do you say?
You want to maybe
be my friend?
Huh?
What did you say?
What did you say, my ass?
Don't be stupid.
Yeah, well,
don't be stupid yourself, stupid.
I'm already your friend, right?
We all already
are your friends.
It was then I realized.
Ten years ago,
it happened all over again.
You're wrong.
I'll prove I'm not weak.
Except this time,
Sora's not here.
Neither is proud little Taka,
for that matter.
It's just weak,
pathetic,
probably fractured
Kotika Hasegawa.
Rika,
will you help me, please?
Sure thing.
Well, this is one
for the Neighbors Club
history books.
We made friends.
Hey, Senna.
I wanted to...
I'm leaving on a journey.
Please don't come looking for me.
What?
Of course.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Looks like our tragically flawed
youth isn't over just yet.
I'll see you next time.